<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sudoku</string>
    <string name="new_game">New Game</string>
    <string name="resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="won_games_perc">Won Games Percentage</string>
    <string name="games">Games</string>
    <string name="games_played">Games Played:</string>
    <string name="games_won">Games Won:</string>
    <string name="games_lost">Games Lost:</string>
    <string name="games_started">Games Started:</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="best_time">Best Time:</string>
    <string name="av_time">Average Time:</string>
    <string name="score">Score</string>
    <string name="best_score">Best Score:</string>
    <string name="av_score">Average Score:</string>
    <string name="rule1">Rule 1</string>
    <string name="rule1_subtitle">Each row must contain the numbers from 1 to 9, without repetitions</string>
    <string name="rule2">Rule 2</string>
    <string name="rule2_description">The Sudoku rules for the columns on the grid are exactly the same as for the rows.\nThe player must also fill these with the numbers from 1 to 9, making sure each digit occurs only once per column.\nThe numbers allocated at the beginning of the puzzle work as clues to find which digits are missing in each column and their position.
    </string>
    <string name="rule2_subtitle">Each column must contain the numbers from 1 to 9, without repetitions</string>
    <string name="rule3">Rule 3</string>
    <string name="rule3_description">A regular 9 x 9 grid is divided into 9 smaller blocks of 3 x 3, also known as nonets.\nThe numbers from 1 to 9 can only occur once per nonet.\nIn practice, this means that the process of filling the rows and columns without duplicated digits finds inside each block another restriction to the numbers’ positioning.
    </string>
    <string name="rule3_subtitle">The digits can only occur once per block (nonet)</string>
    <string name="rule4">\"Rule 4 \"</string>
    <string name="rule4_description">
        To find out which numbers are missing from each row, column or block or if there are any duplicates, the player can simply count or flex their math skills and sum the numbers.\nWhen the digits occur only once, the total of each row, column and group must be of 45.\n1+2+3+4+5+6+7+8+9= 45
    </string>
    <string name="rule4_subtitle">The sum of every single row, column and nonet must equal 45</string>
    <string name="rule1_description">The player must focus on filling each row of the grid while ensuring there are not duplicated numbers.\nThe placement order of the digits is irrelevant.\nEvery puzzle, regardless of the difficulty level, begins with allocated numbers on the grid.\nThe plyer should use these numbers as clues to find which digits are missing in each row.
    </string>
    <string name="show_timer">Show Timer</string>
    <string name="show_score">Show Score</string>
    <string name="hints">Hints</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark Theme</string>
    <string name="game_settings">Game</string>
    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="hints_setting_desc">Enable or disable hints during the game</string>
    <string name="difficulty">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="no_started_games_found">No started games found</string>

</resources>