<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sudoku</string>
    <string name="new_game">Nuova Partita</string>
    <string name="resume">Riprendi</string>
    <string name="statistics">Statistiche</string>
    <string name="settings">Opzioni</string>
    <string name="won_games_perc">Percentuale di Partite Vinte</string>
    <string name="games">Partite</string>
    <string name="games_played">Partite Giocate:</string>
    <string name="games_won">Partite Vinte:</string>
    <string name="games_lost">Partite Perse:</string>
    <string name="games_started">Partite Iniziate:</string>
    <string name="time">Tempo</string>
    <string name="best_time">Miglior Tempo:</string>
    <string name="av_time">Tempo Medio:</string>
    <string name="score">Punteggio</string>
    <string name="best_score">Miglior Punteggio:</string>
    <string name="av_score">Punteggio Medio:</string>
    <string name="rule1">Regola 1</string>
    <string name="rule1_subtitle">Ogni riga deve contenere numeri da 1 a 9, senza ripetizioni</string>
    <string name="rule2">Regola 2</string>
    <string name="rule2_subtitle">Ogni colonna deve contenere numeri da 1 a 9, senza ripetizioni</string>
    <string name="rule3">Regola 3</string>
    <string name="rule3_subtitle">Ogni blocco deve contenere numeri da 1 a 9, senza ripetizioni</string>
    <string name="rule4">\"Regola 4 \"</string>
    <string name="rule4_subtitle">La somma di ogni singola riga, colonna e blocco deve essere pari a 45</string>
    <string name="rule1_description">
        Il giocatore deve riempire ogni riga della griglia assicurandosi che non ci siano numeri duplicati. L\'ordine in cui i numeri vengono inseriti è irrilevante.
        Ogni schema, a prescindere dalla difficoltà, presenta all\'inizio dei numeri già allocati. Il giocatore deve usare questi numeri come indizi per trovare i numeri mancanti in ogni riga.
    </string>
    <string name="rule2_description">The Sudoku rules for the columns on the grid are exactly the same as for the rows. The player must also fill these with the numbers from 1 to 9, making sure each digit occurs only once per column.
        The numbers allocated at the beginning of the puzzle work as clues to find which digits are missing in each column and their position.
    </string>
    <string name="rule3_description">A regular 9 x 9 grid is divided into 9 smaller blocks of 3 x 3, also known as nonets. The numbers from 1 to 9 can only occur once per nonet.
        In practice, this means that the process of filling the rows and columns without duplicated digits finds inside each block another restriction to the numbers’ positioning.
    </string>
    <string name="rule4_description">
        To find out which numbers are missing from each row, column or block or if there are any duplicates, the player can simply count or flex their math skills and sum the numbers. When the digits occur only once, the total of each row, column and group must be of 45.
        1+2+3+4+5+6+7+8+9= 45
    </string>
</resources>